Guide to the AFSCME, Local 420, Hospital Workers Photographs PHOTOS.212
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Black and White Prints
  - Subseries C: Local 420
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries h: Elmhurst Hospital
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation Hearing Elmhurst Hospital, Sep 1999 (Box 9, Folder 402)
      - Elmhurst Campaign (Equal Pay), undated (Box 9, Folder 403)
      - [Elmhurst Hospital -- Justice for Milton Clayton Demonstration], undated (Box 9, Folder 404)
      - [Elmhurst Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 9, Folder 405)
      - [Elmhurst Hospital -- Rally to Reopen the Employee Cafeteria], undated (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries i: Gouverneur Hospital
      - Rally Gouverneur Hospital, Apr 7, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 407)
      - Gouverneur Hospital Campaign, undated (Box 9, Folder 408)
      - Gouverneur Hospital Justice for Delores Benejan, undated (Box 9, Folder 409)
      - [Gouverneur Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries j: Greenpoint Hospital
      - [Greenpoint Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries k: Harlem Hospital
      - [Harlem Hospital Rally -- Mayor Koch; probably 1984] (Box 9, Folder 412)
      - Harlem Hospital Center, May 16, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 413)
      - Employee Service Recognition Day in Harlem Hospital, May 17, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 414)
      - Harlem [Hospital] Graduation [See Folder #774 for some matching negatives.], Mar 24, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 415)
      - Harlem Hospital Bed Cuts -- Meeting, Feb 6, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 416)
      - Med-Surg Techs Harlem [Hospital], Apr 8, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 417)
      - Belinda Perry Award Ceremony/ [Harlem Hospital Graduation; probably 11/1990], Nov 1990 (Box 9, Folder 418)
      - National Health Infrastructure Net Act (Rally at Harlem Hospital) [Spring 1992] (Box 9, Folder 419)
      - Harlem Hospital Social-Psych Techs Graduation, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 420)
      - [Harlem Hospital Rally; probably 1994 or after] (Box 9, Folder 421)
      - Zonzie Moore Harlem Hospital, Jan 5, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 422)
      - Housekeepers Week Harlem Hospital (09-13-94 -- 09-16-94), Sep 13, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 423)
      - Save Harlem Hospital [Rally at] St. Mary's Church, Sep 26, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 424)
      - Save Harlem Hospital, Sep 29, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 425)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally No Medicaid Cut, Jan 30, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 426)
      - All Night Vigil Harlem Hospital, May 15, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 427)
      - No Layoff Rally Harlem Hospital, Apr 1, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 428)
      - Press Conference Harlem Hospital, Apr 10, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 429)
      - Community Support(s) Harlem Hospital, Apr 15, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 430)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally Jesse [Jackson], Sharpton, Apr 22, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 431)
      - No Layoffs DC 37 Meeting [Harlem Hospital], Apr 24, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 432)
      - D[octors] Support Harlem Hospital, Apr 28, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 433)
      - Rally Harlem Hospital [Columbia University], May 20, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 434)
      - Harlem Hospital [Rally], May 28, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 435)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally, Jun 24, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 436)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation Rally (Harlem Hospital), Jun 30, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 437)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally, Jul 8, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 438)
      - Rally Harlem Hospital, Jul 21, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 439)
      - [Rally and Prayer Service to Save Harlem Hospital at Metropolitan AME Church], Dec 7, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 440)
      - No Layoffs (Rally) Harlem Hospital [Sarah Kennedy], Jan 23, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 441)
      - Harlem Hospital[Rally] 6/24 [year unknown], undated (Box 9, Folder 442)
      - Harlem Hospital Bed Cuts [Petition], undated (Box 9, Folder 443)
      - Harlem Hospital Betsy Riviera, undated (Box 9, Folder 444)
      - Harlem Hospital Center, undated (Box 9, Folder 445)
      - [Harlem Hospital Demonstration -- Can't Take Reagan's Budget Cuts. 1980s?], undated (Box 9, Folder 446)
      - Harlem Hospital Graduation, undated (Box 9, Folder 447)
      - Harlem [Hospital] Graduation, undated (Box 9, Folder 448)
      - Marcos Prayer Vigil (Harlem Hospital), undated (Box 9, Folder 449)
      - [Harlem Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 9, Folder 450)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally, undated (Box 9, Folder 451)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally, undated (Box 9, Folder 452)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally, undated (Box 9, Folder 453)
      - Harlem Hospital [Rally], undated (Box 10, Folder 454)
      - Rally at Harlem Hospital, undated (Box 10, Folder 455)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally/Meeting Flyers, undated (Box 10, Folder 456)
      - Nursing Ceritifcation Event[s Harlem Hospital], undated (Box 10, Folder 457)
      - Save Harlem Hospital Campaign/No Privatization, undated (Box 10, Folder 458)
      - Save Harlem Hospital Rally, undated (Box 10, Folder 459)
      - [Stop Misusing Money -- Stop Ripping off Harlem Hospital Rally], undated (Box 10, Folder 460)
      - [Victory Celebration at Harlem Hospital], undated (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries l: Jacobi Medical Center
      - Jacobi Hospital [Rally], Feb 12, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 462)
      - No Layoffs Jacobi Hospital, Apr 8, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 463)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation Hearing -- Jacobi Hospital, undated (Box 10, Folder 464)
      - N[urses] A[ides]' Graduation Jacobi Hospital, undated (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries m: Kings County Hospital
      - K[ings] C[ounty] H[ospital] Press Conf. Re: Psych Deaths, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 466)
      - Kings County Hospital Protest Against Downstate Affiliation, Nov 7, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 467)
      - [Kings County Hospital Center -- Employee Recognition Day], Jun 16, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 468)
      - Kings County Graduation, Apr 25, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 469)
      - Kings County Hospital Grad[uation], May 8, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 470)
      - Kings County Hospital Grad[uation], Jan 22, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 471)
      - Kings County Hospital, undated (Box 10, Folder 472)
      - Kings County Hospital I.V. Tech Graduation, undated (Box 10, Folder 473)
      - [Kings County Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries n: Lincoln Hospital
      - Open Lincoln AIDS Ward [Demonstration], Mar 29, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 475)
      - Lincoln Hospital Press Conference with Governor Mario Cuomo, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 476)
      - Lincoln Hospital "Opening of 27 Bed AIDS Unit", 1991 (Box 10, Folder 477)
      - [Barondess Commission Hearings -- Lincoln and Kings County Hospitals], 1992 (Box 10, Folder 478)
      - Lincoln Hospital Barondess Commission Hearing, Jun 23, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 479)
      - Ribbon Cut -- Lincoln Hospital, Apr 29, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 480)
      - Lincoln Housekeepers Day, Sep 24, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 481)
      - 27 AIDS Bed Unit [Lincoln Hospital], undated (Box 10, Folder 482)
      - [Lincoln Hospital Demonstration], undated (Box 10, Folder 483)
      - Lincoln Hospital Exterior Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 484)
      - Lincoln Hospital N[urses] A[ides] Grad[uation] to M[edical] S[urgical] T[echnician], undated (Box 10, Folder 485)
      - [Lincoln Hospital -- Miscellaneous ], undated (Box 10, Folder 486)
      - Pres. Butler Congratulating the new Exec. Dir. Of Lincoln Hospital Carlos Molina, undated (Box 10, Folder 487)
      - Voices [of] 420 -- Lincoln Hospital Mourns Thelma Richards, undated (Box 10, Folder 488)
      - Voices of 420 (in Concert at Lincoln Hospital), undated (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries o: Metropolitan Hospital
      - Metropolitan Rally No McDonald's, Mar 13, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 490)
      - Met Rally (Metropolitan Hospital) [No McDonald's], Oct 27, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 491)
      - Met[ropolitan Hospital?] Chapter Meeting, Sep 1999 (Box 10, Folder 492)
      - Employee Lounge Met[tropolitan Hospital?], Sep 23, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 493)
      - [Metropolitan Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries p: Neponsit Hospital
      - Rally City Hall Park Save Neponsit, Oct 7, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 495)
      - Press Conference HHC with Mark Green [(Neponsit Hospital)], Oct 29, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 496)
      - (Neponsit) Victory Rally, Nov 4, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 497)
      - Giuliani (Rally on privatization Neponsit Central Laundry Fast Food), undated (Box 10, Folder 498)
      - Neponsit [Rally], undated (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries q: North Central Bronx Hospital
      - Protest Against Women using heavy mops [?] at North Central Bronx [Probably 12/19/1986], Dec 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 500)
      - North Central Bronx (Black History Month), Feb 24, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 501)
      - North Central Bronx Retirement Samy [Samuel Fall], May 26, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 502)
      - Henry Wapple Retire[ment from North Central Bronx], Jun 19, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 503)
      - North Central Bronx Hospital [Rally], Apr 20, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 504)
      - North Central Bronx Hospital [Rally], May 12, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 505)
      - North Central Bronx Rally Not for Sale, Jul 15, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 506)
      - City Hall Hearing North Central Bronx, Aug 10, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 507)
      - North Central Bronx [Demonstration], Aug 16, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 508)
      - North Central Bronx Hospital Rally, Sep 21, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 509)
      - North Central Bronx (Rally), Nov 17, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 510)
      - [Demonstration to Save North Central Bronx Hospital (sun is shining)], undated (Box 10, Folder 511)
      - [North Central Bronx Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 10, Folder 512)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries s: Queens General Hospital
      - Queens General [Hospital] Grievance, Aug 1984 (Box 10, Folder 513)
      - Barondess Commission Hearing Queens General [Hospital] [Probably 1992] (Box 10, Folder 514)
      - Queens General [Rally], Jun 30, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 515)
      - Retirement Queen[s] General [Herbert Carpenter], Mar 19, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 516)
      - Queens General Tech Grad[uation], Jun 29, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 517)
      - [Gwendolyn Hooks Retirement Party -- Queens Hospital Center], Feb 26, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 518)
      - Queens Rally Queens General, Mar 14, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 519)
      - Queen[s] General Press Conference, Aug 7, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 520)
      - Queens General HHC Hearing, Feb 25, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 521)
      - Queens General Rally No McDonalds, Apr 2, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 522)
      - Queens [Hospital Center] Rally No McDonald's, Jun 26, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 523)
      - Queens [Hospital Center] Rally [No McDonald's], Oct 21, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 524)
      - Queens [Hospital Center] Rally (No McDonald's), Nov 5, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 525)
      - Queen Hospital [Center] Rally [No McDonald's], Jun 18, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 526)
      - Queens Hospital [Is Not for Sale Rally], undated (Box 11, Folder 527)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries t: Sea View Hospital
      - Sea View Hospital -- Retirement R. Dalson, Apr 28, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 528)
      - Staten Island [Sea View Hospital] Rally, Mar 30, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 529)
      - Sea View Hospital Graduation, Aug 1, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 530)
      - Sea View Hospital Barondness Commission Hearing, undated (Box 11, Folder 531)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries u: Sydenham Hospital
      - [Sydenham Hospital Demonstration], 1980 (Box 11, Folder 532)
      - Brown, Wm. C. [-- Sydenham Hospital], undated (Box 11, Folder 533)
      - [Sydenham Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 11, Folder 534)
      - Save Sydenham Hospital Rally, undated (Box 11, Folder 535)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries v: Woodhull Hospital
      - Woodhull PCT Graduation, Mar 14, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 536)
      - Woodhull [Hospital] Rally No McDonald's, Aug 27, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 537)
      - [Woodhull Hospital Rally -- Justice and Respect], undated (Box 11, Folder 538)
      - [Woodhull Hospital Rally re: Cafeteria/Parking], undated (Box 11, Folder 539)
      - Goodman Retire/Woodhull Graduation, undated (Box 11, Folder 540)
      - [Woodhull Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 11, Folder 541)
    - Sub-subseries xiii: Worksite
      - [Local 420 -- Cafeteria Workers], undated (Box 11, Folder 542)
      - [Local 420 -- Custodial Workers], undated (Box 11, Folder 543)
      - [Local 420 -- Laundry Workers], undated (Box 11, Folder 544)
      - [Local 420 -- Medical Surgical Technicians], undated (Box 11, Folder 545)
    - Sub-subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries a: General"
      - Asian Pacific Conference San Francisco, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 546)
      - [NYC (Chapter) Labor Council for Latin American Advancement Convention], undated (Box 11, Folder 547)
      - [Awards Presentation -- Central Baptist Church], Sep 22, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 548)
    - Sub-Subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries b: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists
      - CBTU Convention (Memphis) (05/26/82 -- 05/31/82), May 26, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 549)
      - CBTU [5th Annual Awards Dinner Dance], Feb 12, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 550)
      - Black Worker Meeting [CBTU, Chicago, May 26-30, 1983], May 26, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 551)
      - CBTU [Annual Convention May 25-28, 1984], May 25, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 552)
      - CBTU St Louis [/ Shell Boycott, Anti-Apartheid, St. Louis], 1987 (Box 11, Folder 553)
      - CBTU (New York), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 554)
      - [CBTU -- Conference on Healthcare in the Black and Poor Communities; probably 1992] (Box 11, Folder 555)
      - [CBTU 23rd Annual Convention (5-26-94 - 5-30-94)], May 26, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 556)
      - CBTU [25th Anniversary] Convention (5-23-96 -- 5-27-96), May 23, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 557)
      - CBTU [Labor and the Minority Community Conference], May 28, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 558)
      - CBTU ["The Time is Now" Campaign], May 1, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 559)
      - [CBTU Conference -- Coalition Solidarity], undated (Box 11, Folder 560)
      - [CBTU Conference -- The Black Worker: "Meeting the Challenges of the 90's"], undated (Box 11, Folder 561)
      - CBTU Convention, undated (Box 11, Folder 562)
      - [CBTU Meeting? At Omni Shoreham Hotel in Washington, D.C.], undated (Box 11, Folder 563)
      - [CBTU -- Miscellaneous] [See Folder #783 for some matching negatives.], undated (Box 11, Folder 564)
      - CBTU Solidarity Conference], undated (Box 11, Folder 565)
      - CBTU Women's Committee, undated (Box 11, Folder 566)
    - Sub-Subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries c: Coalition of Labor Union Women
      - CLUW [Convention] (04/29/82 -- 05/01/82) [See Folder #778 for some matching negatives.], Apr 29, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 567)
      - [CLUW Honor President Butler], Oct 31, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 568)
      - CLUW Convention, undated (Box 11, Folder 569)
      - [CLUW -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 11, Folder 570)
    - Sub-Subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries d: Labor Research Association Council
      - Labor Research Association [Conference], undated (Box 11, Folder 571)
    - Sub-Subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries e: National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
      - NAACP Voter Registration Hanover County, VA (8/19/84 - 9/1/84), Aug 19, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 572)
      - NAACP [South Bronx Branch Celebration], undated (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Sub-Subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries g: New York City Central Labor Council
      - Central Labor Council Forum, undated (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Sub-Subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries h: Transport Workers Union of America
      - TWU [Transport Workers Union of America] Honors Pres. Butler, May 8, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 575)
- Series II: Color Prints
  - Subseries A: AFSCME
    - AFSCME Convention Las Vegas, Nevada, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 576)
    - [AFSCME 33rd International Convention -- Hawaii (8-24-98 - 8-28-98)], Aug 24, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 577)
    - AFSCME Women's Conference, Jul 3, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 578)
  - Subseries B: AFSCME -- District Council 37
    - Hillary Clinton [Speaks at] DC 37, Oct 16, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 579)
    - [DC 37 & Local 420 -- Politicians with Union Officials], undated (Box 12, Folder 580)
  - Subseries C: Local 420
    - Sub-subseries i: General
      - [Local 420 Members], undated (Box 12, Folder 581)
      - [Voices of 420] 420 Choir, undated (Box 12, Folder 582)
      - [Miscellaneous -- Unidentified and Unknown], undated (Box 12, Folder 583)
    - Sub-subseries ii: Celebrations
      - [Martin Luther King Jr. Celebration, Memphis, Tenn.], Apr 4, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 584)
      - Institutional Dietary Aides Halloween Party, Oct 1993 (Box 12, Folder 585)
      - [Christmas Concert Voices 420], Dec 19, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 586)
      - Christmas Party, Dec 19, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 587)
      - Black History Month Celebration, Feb 11, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 588)
      - [Birthday Party for Person Unknown -- Possibly in Bermuda], undated (Box 12, Folder 589)
      - Cultural Celebration, undated (Box 12, Folder 590)
      - Hispanic Heritage Cultural Celebration, undated (Box 12, Folder 591)
      - [Miscellaneous Celebrations (Retirements, Birthdays, Awards, Honors)], undated (Box 12, Folder 592, Box Shared Tamiment 019)
    - Sub-subseries iii: Committees
      - Women's Committee (Local 420) [Probably 1989] (Box 12, Folder 593)
      - Youth Committee, Jun 1, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 594)
    - Sub-subseries iv: Demonstrations and Rallies
      - Hamlet, May 2, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 595)
      - Harlem [Hospital] Rally/[Cleveland] Robinson [funeral or memorial], Aug 30, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 596)
      - [Justice for Abner Louima -- Preparation for Demonstration and Demonstration; probably 1997] (Box 12, Folder 597)
      - Gracie Mansion Rally, Oct 8, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 598)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation Rally [Cafeteria Workers], Oct 30, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 599)
      - Support Strawberry Workers, Nov 25, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 600)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation Rally, Jun 8, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 601)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation Rally, Jul 16, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 602)
      - Rally City Hall Park, Aug 5, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 603)
      - [Rally and Prayer Service to Save Harlem Hospital at Metroplitan AME Church], Dec 7, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 604)
      - Rally HHC -- Stop Contract[ing Out Jobs], Sep 2000 (Box 12, Folder 605)
      - AFSCME & Local 420 [Support Mushroom Farmers], undated (Box 12, Folder 606)
      - [AFSCME Supports the Frontier Hotel Strikers -- Las Vegas [1991-1997]], undated (Box 12, Folder 607)
      - ["Arrest Giuliani" Demonstration], undated (Box 12, Folder 608)
      - Labor Rally in Church [See Folder # 781 for some matching negatives.], undated (Box 12, Folder 609)
      - [No Budget Cuts Rally held in Memorial Baptist Church], undated (Box 12, Folder 610)
      - [No Layoffs Demonstration (in Albany?) 1990s?], undated (Box 12, Folder 611)
      - [Protest/Rally at the Capitol Building in Albany], undated (Box 12, Folder 612)
      - Rally 125 Worth Street [WEP "Workfare"], undated (Box 12, Folder 613)
      - [Rally for Susan Smith McKinney Nursing and Rehabilitation Center Workers], undated (Box 12, Folder 614)
      - [Save Our Public Hospitals Rally. 1990s?], undated (Box 12, Folder 615)
      - Stop Police Brutality -- [Justice for] Diallo [Rally], undated (Box 12, Folder 616)
      - [Tuberculosis Rally -- Governor Mario Cuomo], undated (Box 12, Folder 617)
      - [undated Demonstrations and Rallies] (Box 12, Folder 618)
    - Sub-subseries v: Events, Sub-sub-subseries a: General
      - International Labor Communication Association Award [to Photographer Marshall McCullen] [Probably 1984. See also folder #s 136 & 266] (Box 12, Folder 619)
      - WEP ["Workfare"] Worker Rally City Hall, Jan 15, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 620)
      - BPRC [Black Puerto Rican Celebration?] Weekend, Feb 16, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 621)
      - [Tribute to] Reverend Councilman Wendell Foster, Feb 8, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 622)
      - Black and Puerto Rican Weekend, Feb 12, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 623)
      - [Memorial Tribute? to] James Farmer [at City Hall?], Jul 21, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 624)
      - Win [Local 420 Election?], Aug 19, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 625)
      - Turkey Day 420 NBC USA, Nov 17, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 626)
      - [A Funeral - Gravesite. Probably 2000.] (Box 12, Folder 627)
      - Turkey Day, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 628)
      - Event at the Sheraton [Hotel], undated (Box 12, Folder 629)
      - Martin Luther King Jr. High School [Voices of 420 Concert], undated (Box 12, Folder 630)
      - [Memorial Services for Patrick Dorismond], undated (Box 12, Folder 631)
      - Press Conferences, undated (Box 12, Folder 632)
      - [Unidentified Event in Church, James Butler Present], undated (Box 12, Folder 633)
    - Sub-subseries v: Events, Sub-sub-subseries b: Charity
      - Voices 420 "Jamaica Relief Concert" Memorial Baptist Church, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 634)
      - Hurricane [Hugo] Victim Support [Probably 1989] (Box 13, Folder 635)
      - Mother Hale/ Hale House Fundraiser, Aug 25, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 636)
      - [Concert and Fundraiser for the Victims of Hurricane Georges], Oct 9, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 637)
      - Concert for Flood Victims North Carolina, Nov 10, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 638)
      - Hurricane Relief Rocky Mount, North Carolina, Nov 12, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 639)
      - [Charity -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 13, Folder 640)
    - Sub-subseries vi: Hearings
      - City Council Health Committee Hearing, Mar 12, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 641)
      - State Hearing Health and Hospitals Corporation, Oct 1, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 642)
      - [Hearings -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 13, Folder 643)
    - Sub-subseries vii: International Friendships/Solidarity
      - [Antigua Workers Union, 30th Anniversary Banquet], May 31, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 644)
      - Antigua [Workers Union, 33rd Annual Delegates Conference], Sep 19, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 645)
      - Bermuda Industrial Union 50th Year Anniversary [See Folder #782 for some matching negatives.], undated (Box 13, Folder 646)
      - [Bermuda Industrial Union Banquet], undated (Box 13, Folder 647)
      - [Bermuda Industrial Union?] Labor Day, undated (Box 13, Folder 648)
      - [Welcome Sister Khumbu Mtinanza of South Africa], undated (Box 13, Folder 649)
    - Sub-subseries viii: Local Officers
      - Butler, James honored by Phi Beta Sigma Fraternity (4-23-92 -- 4-26-92), Apr 24, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 650)
      - Butler, James Honored by DC 1707 [Probably 10/1993], Oct 1993 (Box 13, Folder 651)
      - Butler, James' 25 Years Anniversary, Oct 11, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 652)
      - Butler, James [accepting award from] Assemblyman Nick Perry, Oct 15, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 653)
      - [Butler, James Presented Award by King Emanuel Baptist Church], Oct 14, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 654)
      - [Butler, James Presented Award by the Grace Congregational Church of Harlem], undated (Box 13, Folder 655)
      - Butler, James honored by Friends of Helen Foster, undated (Box 13, Folder 656)
      - Butler, James & Ensley Campaign [Vote], undated (Box 13, Folder 657)
      - Butler, James & Friends, undated (Box 13, Folder 658)
      - Butler, James (President), undated (Box 13, Folder 659)
      - Butler, James' 20th Anniversary, undated (Box 13, Folder 660)